calendar-12.com 2016-11-29

# Privacy Policy - Calendar-12.com

This privacy policy is for this website (www.calendar-12.com) and governs the privacy of its users who choose to use it. 

## Personal Information

We do not gather personal data about our users other than the personal details they provide when contacting this website through the contact form. We also do not share or disclose the personal details provided with third parties. The data provided is kept private and stored securely until it is no longer required. 

## Use of Cookies

Cookies are small text files stored on the users computers / devices. The files contain information about the usage of the website and preferences concerning website functionality. 

This website uses cookies to improve the users experience while visiting the website. You can turn off the use of cookies at anytime by changing your specific browser settings. 

This website also uses tracking software to monitor it's visitors to better understand how they use it. This software is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The software uses cookies to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website but does not store, save or collect personal information. You can read [Google privacy policy](https://www.google.com/privacy.html "Google privacy policy") for further information. 

### Ads

This website may contain sponsored links and adverts. These will typically be served through our advertising partners, to whom may have detailed privacy policies relating directly to the adverts they serve. 

Clicking on any such adverts will send you to the advertisers website through a referral program which may use cookies and will tracks the number of referrals sent from this website. This may include the use of cookies which may in turn be saved on your computers hard drive. Users should therefore note they click on sponsored external links at their own risk and this website and it's owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any external links mentioned. 

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our website. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the advertising [opt-out page](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

### Further Information

This privacy policy is subject to change without notice and was last updated on Dec, 27, 2013. If you have any questions feel free to contact us directly using the Contact page.
